Mya Zar Cho Frontend Web Developer

Yangon, Myanmar myazarcho@gmail.com +959770565059



PROFILE

Since beginning my journey as a frontend web developer over 3 years ago, I acquired various projects and time management skills, as well as the ability to communicate with team members and clients while effectively meeting milestones and deadlines.

SKILLS

Languages

Javascript, MySQL, JQuery, React, CSS, HTML, PHP (Laravel)

Hard Skill

Programming, Wireframes, Git, Debugging

Soft Skills

Collaboration, Communication, Critical Thinking, Problem Solving, Adaptability

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Frontend Web Developer, Clickr Media (Myanmar) Pte. Ltd.

Responsibilities:

Solid experience with Bootstrap and UIKit

- Used advanced javascript libraries
- Solid knowledge in HTML5, CSS3, SASS or SCSS
- Mobile Responsive Development
- Wordpress and Email templates
- · Understanding of how to troubleshoot common development issues

Web Developer, CDG (Myanmar) Limited

Responsibilities

- $\bullet\,$ Design and implement web applications that use the Laravel framework.
- Understanding of the MVC pattern.
- Understanding of SQL databases.
- · Good interpersonal skills.

Oct 2019 – Jul 2020 Yangon, Myanmar

Oct 2020 - present

Yangon, Myanmar

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science (B.C.Sc), University of Computer Studies

Dec 2014 - Oct 2019 Thaton, Myanmar

Mya Zar Cho 1/1